-=www.niuguo.net=-
- -=牛過論壇www.niuguo.net=- 榮譽出品 本字幕僅供學習交流，嚴禁用於商業途徑
-=NTK group=- www.niuguo.net
-=NTK小組工作室=- 翻譯:lovemovie 校對:lovemovie
Where do you think you're going?
你要去哪兒?
Going home.
回家.
Officer!
警官!
The guy walked into the bushes, maybe to pee, but he never came back.
那傢夥走進了樹叢, 可能是去撒尿, 但沒回來.
Do you need help?
需要幫助嗎?
Do you own this car?
你的車嗎?
That's not him. The guy walked into the bushes.
不是他的. 那傢夥進樹叢了.
He said he was going home.
他說是回家.
Going home?
回家?
Please return to your cars.
請回你的車.
What about the car?
這車怎麽辦?
I'll call a tow truck to get it.
我叫拖車拖走.
Shove it out of the way and get the lane moving!
推出馬路，讓交通通順!
We're in a dangerous environment.
我們的環境很危險.
We got a lot of glass and steel rushing by.
很多車川流不息.
Wait a minute.
等一下.
Prendergast, Downtown Robbery. Let's go.
Prendergast, 市區劫案組. 走吧.
I'm in linoleum tile.
我在瓷磚公司.
All right. You, back in your vehicle.
好的. 你, 回你的車.
You push. I'll steer.
你推. 我駕駛.
We do ceramics too. Special discount for law officers.
我們也做陶瓷. 警官給特別折扣.
I love Cops, the TV show. Don't you watch it? I never miss it.
我愛警察, 那個電視節目. 沒看過嗎? 我從不錯過.
You're lucky you caught me.
你碰到我很幸運.
I am?
是麽?
T oday's my last day as a cop.
今天是我做警察最後一天.
Lucky me.
給我幸運.
Don't touch it!
別碰!
Just get this lane moving.
去讓交通通順.
Okay. Sorry.
好的. 抱歉.
Officer!
警官!
Oh, my God! The phone!
哦, 上帝! 電話!
Come on, baby.
來,寶貝.
Watch your fingers.
小心你的手指.
Take Tucker, okay?
關上門, 好嗎?
Mom?
媽媽?
om, can you help me open this?
媽, 能幫我打開這個嗎?
Can I get some change for the phone?
我能換點零錢打電話嗎?
No change. Have to buy something.
不換. 得買點東西.
-Eighty-fie sen. -What?
-八十幅費. -什麽?
Eighty-fie sen.
八十幅費.
-I don't understand. -Eighty-fie sen.
-我不明白. -八十幅費.
Eighty-five cents?
八十五分?
That won't leave enough for a call.
那麽剩的錢不夠打電話.
I'll give you 50 cents. You give me 50 cents change.
我給你五十分. 你給我五十分零錢.
-No way. -Yes, way.
-不行. -行.
Drink, eighty-fie sen. You pay or go!
喝掉, 八十幅費. 付款走人!
I don't understand the word ""fie."" There's a ""v"" in ""five.""
我不懂這個詞 "幅." 發音不是這樣的
Don't got "v's" in China?
在中國這麽說?
-Not Chinese. I'm lKorean. -Whatever.
-不是中國人. 我是韓國人. -無論什麽.
You come to my country, take my money...
你來到我的國家, 拿我的錢...
...and don't even learn my language?
...卻不學我的語言?
You're lKorean?
你是韓國人?
Do you have any idea how much money my country has given yours?
你知道我們國家給你們國家多少錢嗎?
How much?
多少?
I don't know. It's got to be a lot. You can bet on that.
我不知道. 很多. 可以打賭.
You go now! No trouble!
你馬上離開! 別鬧事!
I stay.
我不走.
What do you think of that?
你怎麽想?
Jesus Christ!
耶穌基督!
What is this? The last stand on Fiji?
這是什麽? 在斐濟?
Take the money! Take the money!
拿錢走! 拿錢走!
Take the money.
拿錢走.
Take your hands away from your-- I can't under-- Stop it!
拿開手-- 我不能-- 停下!
All right. Speak slowly and distinctly.
好的. 慢慢說，清楚點.
Take the money.
拿錢走.
You think I'm a thief?
你覺得我是小偷?
You see, I'm not the thief.
你看,我不是小偷.
I'm not charging 85 cents for a stinking soda! You're the thief!
我不給一瓶臭蘇打付85分! 你是小偷!
I'm just standing up for my rights as a consumer.
我只是在爭取做顧客的權利.
I'm rolling back prices to 1 965. What do you think of that?
我回到1965年的價格. 你怎麽想?
Doughnuts. Package of six. How much?
油炸圈餅. 一包六個. 多少錢?
$ 1. 1 2.
$ 1. 1 2.
Too much.
太貴.
Aspirin. Price?
阿司匹林. 價格?
$3.40.
$3.40.
Oh, please!
哦, 求你!
AA batteries. Package of four.
鹼性電池. 一包四個.
$4.29.
$4.29.
Nice try.
這次好.
I think this whole shelf looks suspect.
我覺得這整個架子有問題.
One soda...
一瓶蘇打...
... 1 2 ounces.
... 1 2 盎司.
50 sen!
50 費!
Sold.
成交.
It's been a pleasure frequenting your establishment.
我會常來光顧.
Very funny.
很搞笑.
Very, very funny.
非常, 非常搞笑.
Genuine Arizona sand, Prendergast. Get used to it.
真正的亞利桑那沙子, Prendergast. 習慣一下.
I bet.
我打賭.
Genuine Santa Monica sand's more like it.
更像真正的莫尼卡海灘沙子.
It's from my cat's litterbox, but he said you could keep the lumps.
是從我貓巢裏拿的, 但他說你可以養鳥.
You took my stuff out first?
你先把我的東西拿出去了?
Heck, no. How fun would that be?
Heck, 不. 那會有趣?
-How am I to get a pen out? -You don't need one. Use a cat turd.
-我怎麽找出一支筆? -你不需要. 用塊貓糞.
It's your last day. Be careful. Remember Forsythe?
這是你最後一天. 小心點. 記得 Forsythe?
Forsythe had five minutes to retirement.
Forsythe 離退休只有五分鐘.
Not even two minutes. The guy was on the way to his fucking car.
沒兩分鐘. 那傢夥就沖向了他的車.
Mowed down by a runaway impound. Nasty.
交通事故玩完了. 噁心.
Ironic.
諷刺.
-lronic as fuck! -Anything can happen today.
-真他媽諷刺! -今天什麽事都可能發生.
You know how dangerous a desk can be.
你知道桌子會有多危險.
Watch out for paper cuts.
小心切紙刀.
Funny, funny, funny.
搞笑, 搞笑, 搞笑.
Sorry. I tried to dissuade them.
抱歉.我勸過他們了.
Hey, Sandra. It's obligatory, I guess.
嗨, Sandra. 這是必須的, 我猜.
Now, what else do they have up their sleeve?
現在, 他們袖筒裏還藏著什麽?
Nothing.
沒什麽了.
Are we still on for lunch? You're not going home early?
還待到吃午飯? 不早點回家?
Why would l?
我爲什麽?
Last day and all.
最後一天和所有的.
I'm not superstitious.
我不迷信.
Ready, Sandy?
準備好了, Sandy?
In a minute.
稍等.
Leave the poor desk jockey alone, will you?
離開那個可憐的辦公桌操作員, 行嗎?
Go see if you can remember how to start the car.
你去看看你還會不會發動車.
Let's not get our pantyhose in a bind.
別把襪子連一塊了.
I'll miss you, Prendergast.
我會想你, Prendergast.
You really will?
真的會?
Me too.
我也是.
Come on, Sand, let's go!
快, Sandy, 我們走!
Lunch?
午飯?
Just a second, baby.
等一下, 寶貝.
When are we going to make the strawberry cake?
你什麽時候去做草莓蛋糕?
Soon. I thought sundown would be good.
很快. 我覺得日落時不錯.
Here. Not in the house.
給. 出去玩.
Just a few kids. I didn't want to do a whole big thing.
只是幾個孩子. 我不想做全套.
Prendergast here.
這兒是Prendergast .
It's me.
是我.
I wish you were home. Couldn't you come home now?
我想你回家. 你不能馬上回家?
What's wrong?
怎麽了?
I don't know.
我不知道.
I just got a little scared and...
我只是有點害怕...
...I'd like you to come home.
...我想要你回家.
What is it, honey?
什麽事, 親愛的?
I don't know. I was wrapping some...
我不知道. 我在包一些...
...some glasses up and some things...
...鏡框和別的...
...and I got really scared.
...我真有點害怕.
You're not doing this move just for me, are you?
你不只是爲我搬家的, 對吧?
I mean, you really want to do it, don't you?
我是說, 你是真的想, 是不是?
The important thing is we're together. That's what counts.
最重要的是我們在一起. 這才管用.
But you're not here.
但是你沒在這兒.
I will be soon, baby.
我會很快的, 寶貝.
Say it.
說.
-Say it! -I'll be home soon!
-說! -我會很快回家!
No, say it!
不, 說!
I'll be home soon, and I love you.
我會很快回家, 我愛你.
I love you too.
我也愛你.
Feel better?
感覺好點?
No, I don't feel better!
不，沒好點!
London Bridge is falling down
倫敦大橋在陷落
Falling down, falling down
陷落, 陷落
London bridge is falling down Help me.
救命.
My fair lady
我的小仙女
Are you my fair lady?
你是不是我的小仙女?
Okay.
好.
-Bye -Bye-bye.
-拜 -再見.
What you doing, mister?
你在幹什麽, 先生?
Nothing.
沒什麽.
You' re trespassing on private property.
你入侵了私人領地.
-T respassing? -Loitering too.
-入侵? -還遊蕩.
That's right. You' re loitering too.
是的. 你還遊蕩.
I didn't see any signs.
我沒看到任何標誌.
What do you call that?
你管這個叫什麽?
Graffiti?
塗鴉?
No, man.
不, 夥計.
That's not fucking graffiti! That's a sign.
不是他媽的塗鴉! 是個標誌.
He can't read it, man.
他看不懂, 夥計.
I'll read it for you. It says this is private property.
我讀給你聽. 上面說這是私人領地.
No fucking trespassing!
不可入侵!
This means fucking you!
這是指他媽的你!
It says all that?
寫著所有這些?
If it was in fucking English, I'd fucking understand it!
如果是他媽的英語, 我他媽的就明白!
-Thinks he's being funny. -I'm not laughing.
-他覺得在搞笑. -我沒笑.
-Me neither. -Hold it, fellas.
-我也沒有. -等等, 夥計們.
We're getting off on the wrong foot.
我們這樣不對.
This is a gangland thing, isn't it?
這是個黑道區域, 是不是?
We're having a territorial dispute?
我們有個領土紛爭?
I've wandered into your pissing ground or whatever the damn thing is...
我走入了你撒尿的地方，或別的他媽的什麽...
...and you're offended by my presence. I can understand that.
...你被我的出現激怒了. 我能明白這些.
I mean, I wouldn't want you people in my back yard, either.
我是說, 我也不希望你們進我的後院.
This is your home, and...
這是你家, 而...
...your home is your home I respect that.
...你家就是你家 我尊重這個.
So if you would just back up a step or two...
所以如果你後退一兩步...
...I'll take my problems elsewhere.
...我帶著我的問題到別處去.
Okay?
好嗎?
Fair enough?
夠公平?
-What do you think? -He should pay a toll.
-你怎麽想? -他得付通行費.
Good idea.
好主意.
You should pay a toll.
你得付通行稅.
Listen, fellas...
聽著, 夥計們...
...I've had a rare morning. I'm not in the mood to--
...我有了個奇特的早晨. 我沒在月球上--
What should he pay?
他該付什麽?
How about that fucking briefcase?
他那他媽的公事包怎麽樣?
Good idea.
好主意.
Give us your briefcase, man.
給我們你的公事包, 夥計.
I'm not giving you my goddamn briefcase.
我不給你們我他媽的公事包.
Motherfucker, give us your motherfucking briefcase!
媽的, 給我們你的他媽的公事包!
I was willing to mind my own business.
我想想想我自己的事.
I was willing to respect your territory and treat you like a man.
我想尊重你們的領土 而且把你們當個人.
You couldn't let a man...
你們不能讓一個先生...
...sit here for five minutes to rest on your precious piece-of-shit hill?
...坐在你珍貴的 小破土丘上休息五分鐘?
Want my briefcase? I'll get it for you, all right?
想要我的公事包? 我拿給你, 好嗎?
You want my briefcase? Here's my briefcase!
你想要我的公事包? 給你我的公事包!
Where are you going?
你們去哪兒?
You forgot the briefcase!
你忘了我的公事包!
I'm going home! Clear the path, you motherfucker!
我要回家! 別擋道, 你他媽的!
Clear the path!
別擋道!
I'm going home!
我要回家!
How'd they do that?
他們怎麽做的?
-Gun! -What?
-槍! -什麽?
You're leaving today, right? I got to get your gun.
你今天要離開, 對吧? 我來收槍.
Right.
對.
I need your John Doe right here, here and here.
我需要你在這兒簽名, 這兒和這兒.
You got time to take a statement?
你到時間交接了嗎?
I know you want to get home before you get killed, but--
我知道你不想回家前被殺, 但是--
Yeah, Brian, I'm still working.
是的, Brian,我還在工作.
This guy's a little excited.
這傢夥有點激動.
Mr. Lee, come on in.
Lee先生, 進來這兒.
What'd he say?
他說什麽?
You know, I don't know. Mr. Lee is lKorean.
你明白,我不知道. Lee先生是韓國人.
I'm Japanese, in case you never bothered to notice.
我是日本人, 你沒注意到.
Speak English, okay?
講英語, 好嗎?
Sit down.
坐下.
He'll help you. Mr. Lee owns a market. He was hit less than an hour ago.
他會幫你. Lee先生有一個商店. 他不到一小時前遭到襲擊.
Sorry, Mr. Lee, no smoking.
抱歉, Lee先生,不能吸煙.
Mr. Lee, let's just start off with what he looked like.
Lee先生, 先講講他長什麽樣.
White man, white shirt, tie.
白人, 白襯衣, 領帶.
-What color was his tie? -Color?
-領帶什麽顔色? -顔色?
I don't know color. The guy attack me, okay?
我不知道顔色. 那傢夥襲擊我, 對吧?
He bust up my store. I'm lucky to be alive.
他襲擊我的商店. 我走運還活著.
Just try and relax. What did he steal from you?
放鬆點. 他偷了你什麽?
Did not steal! Attack me, okay?
沒偷! 襲擊我, 行嗎?
Say he fix my prices. Bust up my merchandise.
他說固定我的價格. 砸了我的貨.
He didn't rob you?
他沒搶你?
The guy crazy. I told him, "T ake my money."
那傢夥瘋了.我跟他說, "拿錢走."
He say no. He call me ""thief,"" then he break up my merchandise.
他說不. 他叫我"小偷" 接著打爛我的貨.
Then he buy a soda and take off.
然後買了一瓶蘇打離開.
He bought a soda. He paid for it?
他買了一瓶蘇打.他付錢了?
I told you, the guy crazy.
我跟你說了, 那傢夥瘋了.
Sorry, I thought this was a robbery.
抱歉, 我以爲是劫案.
Mr. Lee, we have to go talk to somebody else.
Lee先生, 我們得去找別人談談.
You were assaulted. This man works robberies.
你被攻擊. 這人解決劫案.
That's right. Come on.
對的. 走.
-Baseball bat! -What's that?
-棒球棒! -那是什麽?
The guy take my baseball bat.
那傢夥拿走了我的棒球棒.
You sell baseball bats?
你賣棒球棒?
No, keep for defense. Under counter. Defense.
不, 防身用. 櫃檯下面. 防身.
You mean he stole your baseball bat but paid for the soda?
你是說他偷了棒球棒付了蘇打的錢?
This guy's discriminating.
這傢夥還區別對待.
That still doesn't count. Let's go. Thanks.
那也不算. 走吧. 謝謝.
You should go to the hospital. Your arm might be broken.
你該去醫院. 你的胳臂受傷了.
We'll look for this guy, so shut the fuck up!
我們會找到那傢夥, 你他媽閉嘴!
What did this guy do? Threaten you with his credit card?
那傢夥幹什麽了? 用他的信用卡威脅你?
I told you he had a bat!
我說了他有個棒球棒!
If this guy's still around, we'll find him and fuck him up.
如果他還在附近, 我們就會找到他，幹死他.
Then you go to the hospital?
然後你去醫院?
Shut up!
閉嘴!
Cut the crap. I know it's you.
別廢話. 我知道是你.
What do you want?
你想幹什麽?
It is you, isn't it?
是你,不對嗎?
It's me.
是我.
You got to stop calling me.
你不該給我打電話.
It's Adele's birthday....
今天是Adele的生日....
Yes, I know. What do you want?
是的, 我知道. 你想幹什麽?
I'm coming home.
我要回家.
What are you talking about?
你在說什麽?
I just....
我只是....
I want you to know that I'm coming home for her birthday.
我想讓你知道我回家給她過生日.
No, you're not coming here.
不,你不能回這兒.
Listen, Beth...
聽著, Beth...
...I got to see you.
...我得看你.
No, you listen to me. This is my house now. I pay the rent.
不, 你聽我說. 現在這是我的房子. 我付房租.
You don't even pay child support.
你甚至沒付孩子的撫養費.
You can't just walkk in and out.
你不能進進出出.
Don't talk like that, Beth.
別那麽說, Beth.
I have to come home.
我得回家.
I have to bring her a present.
我得給她個禮物.
You know you can't come here!
你知道你不能回這兒!
It's him! It's him, man!
是他!是他,夥計!
How's Adele?
Adele怎麽樣?
This isn't your home anymore.
這裏不再是你家.
How is she?
她怎麽樣?
She's doing just fine without you.
她沒你很好.
-Get out. -Come on, man.
-下去. -來, 夥計.
It's fucking broad daylight! This shit ain't worth it!
這是他媽的光天化日! 這個東西不值得!
-Get the fuck out! -Get out of the car!
-他媽的下車! -下車!
Give me one, give me one.
給我一個,給我一個.
And you?
還有你?
Don't.
別.
I'll call the police if I have to.
如果必要我叫警察.
Go, go, go!
走,走, 走!
I'm coming home.
我要回家.
Did you get him?
你打到他了嗎?
You missed.
你沒打准.
I missed too.
我也沒打准.
Don't fucking do it, man!
別他媽這麽做, 活計!
No, man.
不, 夥計.
Fuck you, motherfucker!
幹你, 媽的!
There, you see?
嗯, 你明白?
That's the concept.
那就是規則.
Take some shooting lessons, asshole!
上些射擊課, 屁眼!
She's open.
門開著.
Have a seat.
坐吧.
Captain.
隊長.
Did you hear?
聽說了嗎?
The drive-by shooting?
駕車槍擊?
Disgusting!
噁心!
You know who'll have to take the heat again...
你知道我們得...
...when the shit hits the fan.
...從新再來.
You're retiring a little early.
你退休有點早.
You won't be getting your full pension.
你拿不到全額退休金.
Yes, sir, that's right. I won't.
是的, 先生, 對的. 我拿不到.
This isn't because you were wounded, is it?
你不是因傷,對吧?
Wounded?
傷?
Because, I mean...
因爲, 我是說...
...you're behind a desk now.
...你現在坐辦公桌.
Not much chance of getting wounded there.
沒太多機會受傷.
Look, captain, it has nothing to do with that.
看,隊長, 這與那個無關.
I'll make my speech.
我要作演說了.
They make me do this, you understand.
他們讓我做這個, 你明白.
I hate to lose a good cop.
我憎恨失去一個好警察.
Not too late to change your mind.
改變主意還不晚.
Lot of good cops want to drop the whole kit and caboodle.
很多好警察想善始善終.
And who wouldn't?
誰不是?
The pay stinks...
薪水發臭...
...and you're up to your ears in human scum 1 6 hours a day.
...一天十六小時把耳朵伸進人渣.
But it gets in your blood.
但它深入了你的血液.
A lot of good cops'll get to the point...
很多好警察要到這一步...
...of slapping their badge down on this desk...
...要把警察徽章放到這張桌子...
...and find they just can't do it. How about you?
...卻發現他們不能這麽做. 你呢?
Will you stick with the team?
是否歸隊?
No, captain. I don't think I will.
不, 隊長. 我想我不會.
Like I say, they make me ask. You understand.
就像我說的, 他們讓我問的. 你明白.
How are the kids?
孩子怎麽樣?
I don't have any.
我沒有.
What the hell?
到底怎麽了?
I'd like to take my stick to some of these clerks.
我得質問那些文職s.
-The file says-- -We lost a child.
-文件說-- -我們失去了一個孩子.
Lost it?
失去它?
Her. Lost her.
她. 失去她.
Yes, of course. Her. That's rough.
是, 當然. 她. 太粗略了.
Well, it can be.
嗯, 可能是.
Yes, sir.
是,先生.
Still married, right?
還結著婚, 對吧?
Yes, sir, I am.
是的,先生, 是的.
That's good.
那很好.
Where you going?
你去哪兒?
-I'm going home. -Not this way.
-我回家. -這條路不行.
-Why not? -Metrorail construction, that's why not.
-爲什麽不? -施工, 這就是爲什麽不.
Go around.
繞道.
Just follow your tootsies.
走過去.
You sure you don't want something? Coffee, soda, something?
你確定不要點什麽? 咖啡, 蘇打, 別的?
No, thank you.
不, 謝謝.
I feel kind of stupid about this.
我覺得這有點愚蠢.
Better safe than sorry.
安全比抱歉好.
That's what I thought.
我也是這麽想的.
You have a restraining order against your husband?
你對你丈夫有個詰制規定?
Ex-husband.
前夫.
He'd show up on the wrong day...
他會在不該出現的日子出現...
...or in the middle of the night, pounding on the door.
...或者午夜, 撞門.
He has this horrendous temper.
他脾氣暴躁.
I didn't know if a restraining order was a good idea...
我不知道詰制規定是不是個好主意...
...if it'd do more harm than good.
...是否會更糟.
But the judge said we should make an example of him.
但使法官說我們該懲罰他.
So he can't come within 1 00 feet of us.
他不能接近我們100英尺.
Or is it yards? Which is it? Feet or yards?
還是碼? 是哪個?英尺還是碼?
That's up to the judge.
那得問法官.
-I thought it was a set thing. -It's at his discretion.
-我覺得是一樣的. -那是他謹慎決定的.
That's interesting.
那很有趣.
Does he drink?
他喝酒嗎?
Oh, I thought you meant the judge!
哦, 我還以爲在說法官!
-No, I wouldn't say so. -Do drugs?
-不,不能這麽說. -吸毒?
But he is prone to violence?
但他又有暴力傾向?
Yeah, I think you could say that.
是的, 我想你可以這麽說.
Did he strike the little girl?
他打過小女孩嗎?
Did he strike you?
他打過你嗎?
Not exactly.
不確切.
Not exactly?
不確切?
There were times when l...
有幾次...
...thought he was going to...
...我覺得他想要...
...but I just didn't want to wait until he got around to it.
...但是我沒等到他實施.
It's hard to explain.
這很難解釋.
He could, I think.
他會的,我想.
You think?
你想?
Hello, sir. How are you today?
哈羅, 先生. 今天怎麽樣?
I'm doing all right.
我很好.
-How about you? -Me? I'm terrible.
-你呢? -我? 我糟透了.
I'm sorry.
我很遺憾.
I came from Santa Barbara, and my friend wasn't home...
我來自巴巴拉海灘, 我朋友不在家...
...and he owes me money...
...他欠我錢...
...so I have no money to go home.
...所以我沒錢回家了.
I'm almost out of gas. I had to sleep in my car.
我幾乎沒油了. 我不得不睡在車裏.
Do you have a few bucks? It would really help me out.
有沒有點錢? 那的確能救我命.
I'll mail it back. Honest.
我會寄還你. 保證.
Let me see your license.
我看看你的駕駛證.
What for?
幹什麽?
It'll have your address on it.
從上面看看地址.
-I don't have a license. -You drove all the way without it?
-我沒有駕駛證. -你來這兒無證駕駛?
Are you a cop?
你是警察嗎?
Let's see your car registration and your car.
讓我看看你的車牌和車.
All right, forget it. Okay, just forget it.
好了, 算了吧. 好, 算了吧.
That's a hell of a way to treat a vet, man.
對付獸醫真難,夥計.
-You're an animal doctor? -No, a veteran. I was in Nam.
-你是獸醫? -不, 老兵.我曾在 Nam.
You must've been 1 0 years old.
你一定大於十歲了.
I meant to say the Gulf.
我是說溝.
Come on! All I'm asking for is a little change.
哎呀! 我只是要點零錢.
I haven't eaten in three days.
我三天沒吃飯了.
Except for this.
除了這個.
Fuck it! Give me some money, man. Just give me some money.
他媽的!給我點錢, 夥計. 給我點錢.
How about a dime? Give it to me.
一角怎麽樣? 給我.
I'm not giving you any.
我什麽也不給你.
-You got a cigarette? -No.
-你有煙嗎? -不.
You got to give me something.
你得給我點東西.
Why don't you try to get a job?
你爲什麽不試試找個工作?
This is my park. I live here.
這是我的公園. 我住這兒.
Who are you, walking through my park with two bags?
你是誰, 帶兩個包穿過我的公園?
I don't got any. Is that fair?
我什麽都沒有. 這公平嗎?
What's in those bags, anyway? Give me one.
包裏有什麽, 不管怎樣? 給我一個.
I could sell those bags and eat for a week with the money.
我賣了你的包可以吃一周.
Come on, you've got two of them. Why do you need two?
來吧, 你有兩個. 你怎麽需要兩個?
You're right.
你是對的.
Here.
給.
-Are you serious? -I don't need it anymore.
-你當真? -我再也不需要了.
All right! Come on, now. Come on! What the--
好吧! 來吧,現在.來吧!
Son of a bitch!
狗娘養的!
-Can we cut the crap this time? -I'm telling you the truth!
-能不能別廢話? -我在說實話!
Yeah, right.
是, 是的.
-What's up? -She was at the drive-by shooting.
-怎麽了? -她在駕駛槍擊案那兒.
-Who hit your guys? -I told you.
-誰打了你的朋友? -我告訴你了.
We know. The big bad white man. We're not buying it.
我們知道. 大個壞白人. 我們不是買東西.
Who are you protecting?
你在保護什麽?
They put your boyfriend in the hospital. He's probably dead.
他們送你男朋友進醫院了. 他大概死了.
Do you realize that? He's probably fucking dead!
你明白嗎? 他大概他媽的死了!
Stop saying that!
別那麽說!
You picked a good day to leave.
你選了個好日子離開.
You want another 3-year-old to get shot in the head?
你想再有一個三歲小孩被打中頭?
Is that what you want?
那是你想要的?
T ell me the truth!
告訴我真相!
I' m telling you the truth!
我正在告訴你真相!
It was a white guy!
是個白人!
-Why would he go after your friends? -I don't know!
-他爲什麽找你朋友? -我不知道!
He attacked them on Angel's Flight Hill with a baseball bat!
他用棒球棒在天翼山打了他們!
A baseball bat? Wait!
棒球棒? 等一下!
Baseball bat. What did this guy look like?
棒球棒. 那傢夥長什麽樣?
I don't know. He looked like you, except...
我不知道. 看起來像你, 除了...
...he was taller and had hair.
...他高點有頭髮.
Good description, Angie.
描述的好, Angie.
Did he wear a white shirt and tie?
他是不是白襯衣打領帶?
Come over here, will you?
來這兒,行嗎?
We got to keep the pressure on her. Don't interrupt.
我們正在給她施壓. 別打擾.
What about the baseball bat?
棒球棒怎麽回事?
-The white shirt and tie! -What will she think of next?
-白襯衣打領帶! -她下面又會出來什麽?
I' m sorry you' re leaving, but you are.
我很遺憾你要離開了, 但你確實是.
-Listen to me. Listen to me! -Check me later, babe.
-聽我說. 聽我說! -等會問我, 寶貝.
Remember the Korean storekeeper?
記得那個韓國店主嗎?
Come here.
來這兒.
Where was this place?
在哪兒?
Right there.
在這兒.
And he was assaulted sometime after 8 a.m.?
他是八點後遇襲的?
-About that. -And the drive-by was here, right?
-差不多. -槍擊是在這兒, 對吧?
What's going on?
怎麽了?
I may be nuts, but Angel's Flight Hill is between those two spots.
或許我胡說, 但是天翼山在這兩點之間.
-lt was a classy neighborhood. -It's a shit hole. Gangland.
-非常臨近. -那是個屎坑. 黑道區域.
I know. What would a white guy in a shirt and tie be doing in...
我知道. 一個白人白襯衣打領帶會做什麽...
...gangland?
...在黑道區域?
Can I help you?
能爲你服務嗎?
I'd like a ham and cheese Whamlette, an order of Wham fries--
我要一份火腿 芝士蛋糕, 一份薯條--
Sorry, we stopped serving breakfast. We're on the lunch menu.
抱歉, 我們停止早餐了. 現在是午餐時間.
But I want breakfast.
但我想吃早餐.
We' re not serving it.
我們不提供了.
So you said.
你說的.
Is that the manager?
那是你們經理嗎?
Could I speak to him, please?
我能跟他說嗎, 請?
Sure.
當然.
Rick, a customer would like to speak to you.
Rick, 一位顧客想同你講.
Yes, sir?
嗯, 先生?
I'd like some breakfast.
我想要些早餐.
We stopped serving breakfast.
我們停止早餐供應了.
I know you stopped breakfast, Rick. Sheila told me you stopped....
我知道你們停止早餐了, Rick. Sheila 告訴我你們停止....
Why am I calling you by first names? I don't know you.
我爲什麽對你們直呼名字? 我不認識你們.
I call my boss " mister" after seven years, but I walk in here, a total stranger...
我叫我老闆 "先生" 是七年以後, 但我到這兒,完全一個陌生人...
...and I call you Rick and Sheila like we're in some kind of AA meeting.
...而我叫你 Rick 和 Sheila 就像我們在AA會議.
I don't want to be your buddy. I just want a little breakfast.
我不想成爲你的朋友. 我只是想要一小份早餐.
You can call me Miss Folsom if you want to.
你可以叫我 Folsom小姐 如果願意.
We stopped serving breakfast at 1 1 :30.
我們在 1 1 :30停止早餐.
Rick...
Rick...
...have you ever heard the expression, "The customer is always right"?
...你聽沒聽過這句話, "顧客總是對的"?
Well...
嗯...
...here I am.
...我在這兒.
The customer.
顧客.
That's not our policy.
這不是我們的策略.
You have to order something from the lunch menu.
你得從午餐功能表裏選東西.
I don't want lunch.
我不想要午餐.
I want breakfast.
我想要早餐.
Yeah, well, hey, I'm really sorry.
是, 嗯, 嗨, 我很抱歉.
I'm really sorry too!
我也很抱歉!
He's got a gun!
他有槍!
Let's get organized!
我們規整一下!
Calm down!
平靜!
Just calm down, everybody. Sit down over there!
平靜一下, 諸位. 坐那兒!
Mister?
先生?
Where are you going?
你去哪兒?
No. You sit down there, and you finish your lunch.
不. 你坐那兒, 吃完飯.
Everybody just relax and take it easy.
諸位放鬆點.
Why don't you eat your lunch? Please.
你爲什麽不吃你的午餐? 請.
You all need your vitamins A, B and--
你們需要你們的維生素 A, B 和--
Don't! It was an accident!
不! 這是意外!
It's the trigger. It's sensitive. It's okay!
是扳機的事. 太靈敏. 好了!
It's a sensitive trigger.
是個靈敏的扳機.
Could I have my breakfast?
我能吃早餐嗎?
Yes, sir. Sheila?
是, 先生. Sheila?
Rick? Miss Folsom?
Rick?  Folsom小姐?
You know what?
你知道嗎?
You were right. I've changed my mind.
你們是對的. 我改變想法了.
I'm going to have some lunch.
我要吃點午餐.
Could I have a double Whammyburger with cheese--
我要一個雙份芝士漢堡--
-You getting this? -Yes, sir.
-你們做這個? -是的, 先生.
And an order of Whammy fries and, let's see...
一份薯條, 我看看...
...a Choco-Wham shake.
...一個可樂 .
Yes, sir. Sheila, get his order.
是的, 先生. Sheila, 照他說得做.
Rick, could you get it for me, please?
Rick, 能讓你來嗎, 請?
I feel more comfortable calling you Rick...
我覺得叫你Rick更舒服...
...after all we've been through together.
...畢竟我們經歷了這些.
How you doing?
你們怎麽樣?
Enjoying your meal?
吃得好嗎?
How about you, son?
你呢, 小孩?
Is it good?
好嗎?
And you, ma'am? How's the food?
你呢, 老媽媽? 食物怎麽樣?
I think we have a critic.
我想來了個批評家.
I don't think she likes the special sauce.
我想他不喜歡這特製沙司.
That's a joke.
開個玩笑.
Now, here we go.
現在,來吧.
Thank you.
謝謝.
See, this is what I'm talking about.
看, 正是我說的.
Look at that.
看看那個.
See what I mean? It's plump, juicy and three inches thick.
明白我的意思? 它飽滿，多汁，三英寸厚.
Now look at this sorry, miserable, squashed thing.
現在看看這個, 可憐乾癟的東西.
Can anybody tell me what's wrong with this picture?
有人能告訴我這畫怎麽回事嗎?
Anybody?
有人嗎?
Anybody at all.
到底有沒有人.
You guys are partners again!
你們又成搭檔了!
No such luck, Lita. He's moving to Lake Havasu.
沒那麽走運, Lita. 他要搬往Havasu湖.
-What's in Lake Havasu? -London Bridge.
-Havasu湖裏有什麽? -倫敦大橋.
-Are you going to England? -They moved it to Arizona.
-你要去英國? -他們把它搬到了亞利桑拿.
-Stone by stone. -Oh, yeah. I heard about that.
-一塊一塊地. -哦, 是. 我聽說了.
You' re better off, because cops get killed.
你走了更好, 因爲警察正在被殺.
-You usually get six? -Seven.
-你通常選六? -七.
Two sevens.
兩份七號.
You all right?
你還好?
You sure?
你確定?
What?
什麽?
Sorry, I wasn't going to do this.
抱歉,我不想這麽做.
I should just shut up. It's none of my business.
我該閉嘴. 這不關我事.
Tell me.
跟我說.
Lake Havasu?
Havasu湖?
It's nice. We like it.
很漂亮. 我們喜歡.
She likes it.
她喜歡.
What'll you do, watch the cactus grow?
你幹什麽,看仙人掌長大?
Cacti.
仙人掌.
She's not handling middle age too well.
她沒處理好更年期.
The change of life...
生活的變化...
...and all that, whatever it is.
...所有那些, 不管是什麽.
What about you?
你呢?
Me? It's different, because she's a woman.
我? 那不一樣, 因爲她是女人.
What's different? I'm a woman.
什麽不一樣? 我也是個女人.
But she was once very beautiful.
但是她曾很漂亮.
Thanks a lot!
多謝!
You know what I mean. Come on.
你知道我什麽意思. 來吧.
She could have been anything. Anything but a cop's wife.
她可以做好任何事. 所有事除了警察老婆...
She's too high-strung.
她太敏感.
Don't give me that homecoming queen bullshit again.
別再給我說那些.
That was a long time ago.
那是很久以前.
Sandra, you have a career.
Sandra, 你有工作.
It's hard to lose your beauty when that's all you've got.
你不會失去容顔.
What about your career?
你的工作怎麽辦?
I'll be okay...
我會很好...
...even without you.
...即使沒有你.
Sorry to break this up.
抱歉打斷.
-What are you doing here? -We got a call.
-你來這兒幹什麽? -我們有個任務.
Watch out! Hot plates!
小心!盤子!
-Don't touch my gun. -Fuck you!
-別碰我的槍. -他媽的!
You'll love this one. Some dickhead went into Whammyburger...
你會喜歡這個. 一個白癡沖進漢堡店...
...pulled out a gun because they stopped serving breakfast...
...因爲他們停供早餐而掏出一把槍...
...then paid for it and left.
...然後付款走人.
Sorry, Prendergast.
抱歉, Prendergast.
He paid for it?
他付錢了?
Move your buns. Let's go.
挪挪屁股. 我們走.
I gotta go.
我得走了.
Where was this?
這回是哪兒?
Quintero and Fourth. Bye, ladies.
Quintero街四號. 再見, 女士們.
Wait a minute. Wait, wait!
等一下. 等等, 等等!
Let me know what this guy was wearing, okay?
讓我知道他穿什麽,好嗎?
You trying to crack a big one before you disappear into the desert?
你想在消失在沙漠前破個大的?
Sandra, find out if he's wearing a white shirt and tie, okay?
Sandra, 看看他是不是白襯衣打領帶, 好嗎?
Let's go, lovebirds.
走吧, 愛情鳥.
-I got to go. -Wait.
-我得走了. -等等.
Something about my wife. Maybe I never mentioned it.
我老婆的事. 也許我沒提起.
What?
什麽?
I love her.
我愛她.
Let's go!
走吧!
For seven years, I banked here.
七年了, 我存錢在這兒.
When I asked them for a loan, a small loan...
當我要份貸款, 一份小貸款...
...they told me that I was not "economically viable."
...他們告訴我我沒有 "信貸能力."
Excuse me. Excuse me, sir?
打擾. 打擾,先生?
How'd your loan work out? Did they give you a loan?
你的貸款怎麽解決的? 他們給你貸款了嗎?
He must be economically viable!
他一定有信貸能力!
There's a man with a smiling face. A happy customer.
他是個笑容滿面的人. 一個快樂的顧客.
That's what an economically viable person looks like!
這就是有信貸能力的樣子!
How much is the...?
這個多少錢...?
That is only three dollars.
只要三美元.
I asked them for a small loan. You know what they told me?
我沖他們要份小貸款. 你知道他們說什麽?
I was not economically viable.
我沒有信貸能力.
Come on. That's enough.
來. 夠了.
-I'll buy this. -That is three dollars.
-我要買這個. -這個三美元.
This is what happens if you're not economically viable!
這就是沒有信貸能力的下場!
Don't let this happen to you!
別讓這個在你身上重演!
Bye, everybody!
再見, 諸位!
Don't forget me!
別忘了我!
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉.
We're leaving now.
我們要走了.
You are? Really?
你們? 真的?
It doesn't look like your husband's going to show.
你丈夫看起來不會出現.
He probably realized he could get into trouble if he harassed you.
他大概意識到騷擾你會有麻煩.
I think you should call your lawyer and tell him about it.
我想你應該叫你律師告訴他這個.
It's one of those services. I didn't have much money.
這種服務. 我沒有很多錢.
Have them call your husband's lawyer, make it official.
讓她們告訴你丈夫的律師, 公事公辦l.
In the meantime, lock up. And if anything else happens, call us.
同時,鎖好. 有別的事發生, 叫我們.
-Okay, thanks. -Sure thing.
-好的, 謝謝. -沒事.
Excuse me. Hey, excuse me!
打擾.嗨,打擾!
I don't know if you've noticed, but others are waiting to use the phone.
我不知道你是否注意到, 但別人在等著用電話.
-Others want to use the phone? -Right, you asshole!
-別人等著用電話? -是的, 你個屁眼!
Jeez, that's too bad. Because you know what?
呀, 那太糟了. 你知道嗎?
I think it's out of order.
我認爲它壞了.
Hi, it's me.
嗨, 是我.
He's eating and resting comfortably now.
他正在吃東西休息.
-Who is? -Mr. Peepers.
-誰? -Peepers先生.
Good!
好的!
Honey, I'm sorry about before. I really blew my top.
親愛的, 我對剛才抱歉. 我的確發脾氣了.
That's okay, honey. Could you hold on just one second?
沒事, 親愛的. 你能等一會嗎?
Prendergast.
Prendergast.
White shirt and tie.
白襯衣打領帶.
Could you hold on?
你能等會?
I got to go.
我得走了.
Just one second. It's very important.
只一會. 很重要.
Detective Torres? Excuse me?
Torres偵探? 打擾?
We have about 7 million people waiting to make a statement.
大約七百萬人等著我們做聲明.
Let me call you right back.
我等會打給你.
What's wrong? What are you doing?
怎麽了? 你在幹什麽?
Nothing's wrong. What do you mean?
沒什麽. 你什麽意思?
-You come home then. -I can't.
-那麽你回家. -我不能.
It's your last day. What are they going to do, fire you?
今天是你最後一天. 他們會怎麽辦, 解雇你?
There's a lot of red tape. As soon as I get done, I can go home.
很多程式. 我一做完,就能回家.
I'll call you in a while, okay?
我一會打給你,好嗎?
Wait a minute. Make a list.
等一會. 記個單子.
A list?
單子?
We need boneless, skkinless chickken, red bell peppers. Not green, red.
我們需要, 去骨雞, 紅辣椒. 不要青的, 紅的.
Honey, hold on one second.
親愛的, 等一下.
I am tying up the phone here.
我在等著.
Just listen for once in your life.
求你聽著.
A girl at the drive-by said a man in a white shirt and tie...
駕車槍擊案有個女孩說一個人 穿著白襯衣打領帶...
...attacked her homeboys with a baseball bat.
...用棒球棒打了她家的男孩.
I think somebody let that dog off the leash.
我想有人搞錯了.
I think you've got last day-itis.
我想你患了結尾綜合症.
This man was not swinging a bat. He has a gym bag full of guns.
這人沒揮舞棒球棒. 他有一體操包槍.
A gym bag?
體操包?
You asked me to tell you what he wore. Now I got to run.
你要我告訴你他穿什麽. 現在我要走了.
We have to canvas the neighborhood.
我們得去鄰近看看.
One more second.
等一下.
Please. It's important.
求你. 很重要.
-Why don't you go to the store? -Why?
-你爲什麽不能去商店? -爲什麽?
It's my last day.
今天是我最後一天.
The guys might want to have a send off or something.
他們或者會有個歡送什麽的.
What are they going to do? Have some broad...
他們要幹什麽? 舉辦...
...dance topless on your deskk or something?
...舞會還是什麽?
Course not.
當然不是.
Look. While you' re playing cop, l' m at home planning your retirement.
看. 你在做警察玩的時候, 我在家規劃你的退休.
It's over. The sooner you get that through your head, the better.
完了. 最好早點打爆你的頭.
You are no longer in the law-enforcement business.
你不再執行公務了.
Now, I will expect you at the usual time. Capito?
現在, 我在以往時間等你. Capito?
Sandra, are you mad at me?
Sandra, 你快瘋了吧?
-I hate you, but l' m not mad. -Are you retiring too?
-我恨你, 但我沒瘋. -你也退休了嗎?
Just don't leave without saying goodbye.
不說再見別離開.
Goodbye.
再見.
If you go up against this guy...
如果你見到那傢夥...
...be careful.
...小心點.
I'm Nick.
我是 Nick.
What can I do you for?
能爲你做什麽?
I'm just looking for some hiking boots.
我在找徒步旅行靴.
Well, well, hiking boots.
嗯, 嗯, 徒步旅行靴.
Let's see what we got.
看看我們有什麽.
These are the top of the line...
這是頂級品質...
...scientifically engineered and all that crap.
...科學工藝 和所有廢話.
Guaranteed by some Sierra Club asshole not to hurt a chipmunk...
登山俱樂部的屁眼 保證不會傷到花栗鼠...
...if you step on it.
...如果踩上.
Personally, I think they're for pussies and faggots!
個人認爲,這個適合陰道和雞巴!
Now these...
現在這些...
...are Vietnam jungle boots.
...是越南從林靴.
Cost half as much, last twice as long and are great...
價錢一半, 兩倍耐久而且...
...for stomping queers!
...很適合同性戀!
When you're done, you got to clean out the waffle with a stick, but...
當你做完, 你得用棍清理吧, 但是...
...you can't have everything, right?
...你沒法什麽都有, 對吧?
Forget it.
別在意.
Come on, let's go.
來,我們走.
Have a nice day, fellas!
一天愉快, 夥計們!
Y'all come back now, you hear?
你會回來的, 聽到了嗎?
You got a problem, buddy?
你有問題, 夥計?
You got the problem!
你有問題!
-No, you do, buddy! -Read the sign!
-不, 你有, 夥計! -看看標誌!
"l reserve the right."
"我保留權利."
Now take a hike.
現在拿個靴子.
Make me.
給我.
Take it easy, Mary. Take it easy.
放鬆點, Mary. 放鬆.
-Jesus! -Come on, make your play.
-耶穌! -來, 做你們的東西.
Would you just come on! I don't need this shit today.
你馬上要! 我今天不想沾屎.
Fucking redneck!
他媽的農民!
Fascist!
法西斯!
Fucking faggots!
他媽的雞巴!
You believe this shit?
你能相信嗎?
Jesus!
耶穌!
Alternate lifestyle, my ass!
交替著來, 我的屁股!
Imagine what those pumpkins do with each other when they're alone!
想想這些南瓜單獨時會做什麽!
And what about the muff divers? Think about it.
想想那些橡皮手套? 想想.
Sergeant Prendergast.
Prendergast警官.
She don't have to talk!
她不是必須講話!
What do you want! I admitted it was a gang!
你想要什麽! 我承認是一夥!
She don't have to say a word!
她不用講話!
I know it was a white guy. We got to talk. It's important.
我知道是個白人. 我們談談. 這很重要.
How many guns...
多少槍...
...were in the gym bag?
...在體操包裏?
I don't know what you're talking about. I didn't see no gym bag!
我不知道你在說什麽. 我沒看到什麽體操包!
The white guy took it, right? A lot more people could get hurt.
那白人提走了, 對吧? 更多人會受傷.
Now help me out.
現在幫我找出來.
The bag was already in the car when I got in.
我上車時那包就在裏面了.
How many guns were in it?
裏面有多少槍?
I don't know.
我不知道.
Lots of guns.
很多槍.
They got all the guns in the fucking world.
他們在這該死的世界搞到這些槍.
Good?
行嗎?
Can I help you?
能幫你什麽?
Police officer. I'm looking for a man.
警官. 我在找個人.
Are you now?
你現在?
Late 30s...
三十多歲...
...white shirt and tie...
...白襯衣打領帶...
...he'd be carrying a gym bag.
...可能拿一體操包.
What's the police scanner for?
著個警用掃描器幹什麽用?
My own personal amusement.
我的個人消遣.
Have you seen anyone like I've described?
看沒看到我說的人?
Nope.
沒有.
-Okay, thanks. -Listen.
-好的, 謝謝. -聽著.
T ell me something.
跟我說個事.
Why don't they call you guys...
爲什麽他們管你們叫...
...officer-esses?
...女--警官?
I beg your pardon?
什麽?
You know, like act-ress? Like that?
你知道,就像女--招待? 像那個?
Something to signify...
標誌著...
...you know.
...你知道.
I guess they feel that a police officer is a police officer...
我覺得他們覺得警官就是警官...
...not a...
...而不是...
..."you know."
..."你知道."
Thanks for your cooperation, sir.
謝謝合作,先生.
Sorry I couldn't be of more help, officer-ess.
抱歉不能幫更多, 女--警官.
Why'd you do that?
你爲什麽那麽做?
There's something I want to show you.
我有東西給你看.
I'm not going to turn you in. I'm your friend.
我不會把你弄進去. 我是你的朋友.
Come on.
來.
I don't bring just anybody back here, you know.
我從不帶任何人來這兒, 你知道.
This is my own private stash.
這是我的私匿處.
I got some great stuff here.
我這兒有些好東西.
World War l. Good shape.
第一次世紀大戰. 好造型.
Speaking of gas, wait a minute. Wait just a minute.
提到氣, 等一下. 稍等一下.
You know what was in this?
你知道這裏面有什麽?
Zyklon-B.
氫氰酸-B.
You remember?
記得嗎?
What the Nazis had?
納粹有什麽?
Listen.
聽.
Empty.
空的.
This was used, man. This was actually used.
用過了, 夥計. 真是用過了.
I wonder how many kikes this little can took out.
不知道這一小桶搞死多少猶太人.
Think about it. Here.
想想. 給.
Why are you showing me this?
爲什麽給我看這個?
I'm not.
不是.
That's just for fun. You can keep that.
這只是玩玩. 你可以拿著.
This is what I want to show you.
這才是我給你看得.
The real thing.
一個真傢夥.
Heat-seeking, shoulder-fired. It's fucking disposable!
火力足, 肩扛式. 還他媽可拆卸!
You can take out a jet with one of these monkeys.
你可以用這些發泄.
It's for you.
這是給你的.
I want you to have it.
我想你要它.
Why?
爲什麽?
Because I'm with you.
因爲我和你一起的.
Don't you get it? I was listening to the police scanner.
你不要嗎? 我聽著警用掃描器呢.
I heard about the Whammyburger. Fucking fantastic!
我聽說了漢堡店的事. 真他媽荒謬!
It's a bunch of niggers, right? On TV, it's always white kids.
一群黑鬼, 是不是? 電視上, 總是白人孩子.
But when you go in there, it's nothing but a bunch of niggers!
但當你進去, 除了黑鬼沒別的!
They'll spit on your food if you're not nice to them.
他們對你不爽就會吐進食物.
I know all about it.
我全知道.
I'm with you.
我和你一邊.
We're the same, you and me.
我們一樣, 你和我.
Don't you see?
你沒看到嗎?
We are not the same.
我們不一樣.
I'm an American. You're a sick asshole.
我是美國公民. 你是個病鬼.
What kind of vigilante are you?
你是什麽義務警員?
I am not a vigilante.
我不是義務警員.
I'm just trying to get home for my little girl's birthday.
我只是回家給我小女兒過生日.
And if everybody will stay out of my way, nobody will get hurt.
如果大家都不擋我道,沒人會受傷.
Fuck you!
他媽的!
Who the fuck are you? Are you fucking with me?
你他媽是誰? 你在搞我?
I am just disagreeing with you.
我只是不同意你說的.
In America, we have freedom of speech, the right to disagree!
在美國, 我們有言論自由, 也有權不同意!
Fuck you and your freedom!
操你和你的自由!
Who the fuck are you?
你他媽是誰?
You fuck! You faggot fuck!
你他媽! 你個雞巴幹的!
Going to take my rocket.
要拿我的火箭筒.
I ought to shoot you, motherfucker! Now turn around!
我該打死你, 媽的! 現在轉過去!
Now lean on that counter! Go on, lean on it!
現在靠著櫃檯! 來, 靠著!
Look at this shit!
看看這些大便!
What's this doing in there?
這個在這裏面幹什麽?
Faggot shit!
大便!
You want freedom? I'll give you fucking freedom!
你想要自由? 我給你他媽的自由m!
Further back. Feet farther back.
後退. 腳後退.
Spread them out. Farther.
分開. 大點.
You're going to jail, motherfucker! How's that for freedom?
你要進監獄了, 媽的! 自由怎麽樣?
Freedom to get fucked up the ass by some big buck nigger.
被黑鬼的雞巴幹的自由.
Give me your hand. Put it back here.
給我你的手. 放後面.
He's going to be right behind you, just like this.
他會在你正後方, 就像這樣.
Think about it. You going to like that, faggot?
想想吧. 你會像那樣, 雞巴?
You going to like that, you faggot fuck? Give me your other hand.
你會像那樣, 你個雞巴幹的? 給我你另一隻手.
-I can't. -Why not?
-我不能. -爲什麽不?
Gravity.
地心引力.
Gravity? What the fuck does that mean?
地心引力? 那他媽什麽意思?
I'll fall down.
我會倒下.
Now give me your other hand! Give it to me now!
現在給我你另一隻手! 馬上給我!
Give it to me! Give it to me!
給我! 給我!
Come on!
來!
Give it to me!
給我!
This isn't one of mine.
這不是我的.
Oh, my God!
哦, 我的上帝!
Oh...my...
哦...我的...
-...God! -Good!
-...上帝! -好的!
Freedom of religion.
信仰自由.
Now you get the swing of it!
現在你可以走了!
Feels good to exercise your rights.
實踐你的權力感覺不錯.
Go on. I'm listening.
繼續. 我聽著.
We got a nut case with a bag full of guns in Hollywood, heading west.
我們在好萊塢有一個難題，一整包槍, 向西去.
What's he up to?
他要幹什麽?
He's up to a lot of trouble.
他要製造很多麻煩.
Never mind, we've got a hallway full of suspects.
別擔心, 我們有了一走廊嫌犯.
It wasn't a gang thing. I can tell you that.
那不是一回事. 我能告訴你.
Angelina is a tramp and a liar.
Angelina撒謊而且反復.
We don't appreciate you interfering with our investigation.
我們不感謝你打斷我們的調查.
I've got a positive lD on the gym bag, okay?
我得到了那體操包的ID, 好嗎?
What's this?
這是什麽?
A gym bag.
一個體操包.
Does this mean you're putting me under arrest?
這說明你要逮捕我?
You guys take off.
你們拿走.
I gave you that speech earlier...
我向你做那個演說早了些...
...because that's regulations. They make me do it.
...因爲那是規矩. 他們讓我做的.
This one's from me. I've never liked you.
這個是我的. 我從不喜歡你.
You know why? You don't curse. I don't trust a man who doesn't curse.
你知道爲什麽? 你從不粗口. 我不信任一個不粗口的人.
Not a ""fuck"" or a ""shit"" in all these years. Real men curse.
沒有一個"操"或一個"屎"在這麽多年. 真漢子都粗口.
And I don't like a man who's afraid to hit the street.
而且我不喜歡一個害怕在街上撞的人.
-It's bad for morale. -I'm not afraid.
-這對士氣不好. -我不害怕.
Get back behind that desk where you belong...
回你該待的辦公桌後...
...and don't waste any more of my time pretending you're a cop.
...別浪費時間假裝是個警察.
A man in a white shirt and tie...
一個人白襯衣打領帶...
...shot up a phone booth near the Whammyburger.
...在漢堡店槍擊一電話亭.
-Did you hear me? -I heard you.
-聽著麽? -我聽著.
Right about here, right?
在這兒,對吧?
How did you know?
你怎麽知道?
He got the bag of guns at the drive-by.
他在駕車槍擊案那兒得到一體操包槍.
Then you were right.
那麽你是對的.
Excuse me.
打擾.
-What's wrong with you? -Me?
-你怎麽了? -我?
I' m a coward, the captain told me. Get out of my way.
我是個懦夫, 隊長說的. 別當我路.
Hey, look. It is your own fault.
嗨,看.這是你自己的錯.
You let everybody think you were spooked, when it was your wife.
你讓所有人覺得你受到了驚嚇, 事實是你老婆.
She made you get off the street.
她讓你退出.
What happens between me and my wife is nobody's business but mine!
我和我老婆怎麽樣不關別人的事!
Sorry, I've been a bitch all day.
抱歉, 我整天像只母狗.
She didn't make me quit. I came home late one night...
她沒讓我離職. 一天晚上我回家晚了...
...and found her sitting in the dark.
...發現她坐在黑暗中.
She thought I'd been killed.
她以爲我被殺了.
She thought I was a ghost. I had to chase her through the house.
她以爲我是鬼. 我不得不滿房間追她.
-I'm sorry. -Forget it.
-我很抱歉. -別提了.
-Where are you going? -See if I can earn my last day's pay.
-你去哪兒? -看看能不能領最後一天的薪水.
Let me go with you.
我和你一起.
I thought you were on duty.
我以爲你在值班.
What do you say, partner?
你說什麽, 搭檔?
Fuck them!
去他們的!
Go!
走!
Who were you talkking to a while ago?
你剛才跟誰說話呢?
You' re just trying to scare me.
你只是在嚇我們.
Am I succeeding?
我成功了?
No, you're not. So you just might as well stop it.
不,你沒有. 所以你要停下.
And you're not scaring me out of my own house.
你別在我家外嚇我.
And you 're not coming here.
你也別來這兒.
But I am. I ' m on my way. You can count on that.
但我正在. 我在路上. 你要相信.
I ' m past the point of no return.
我過了無歸之點.
Do you know when that is?
你知道是什麽嗎?
That's the point in a journey...
是旅途中的一點...
...where it's longer to go back to the beginning...
...回去比繼續到終點...
...than it is to continue to the end.
...路更長.
It's like....
就像....
Remember when those astronauts got in trouble?
記得宇航員出問題的時候嗎?
They were going to the moon and something went wrong.
他們去月球，突然出問題了.
They had to get back to Earth...
他們不得不回地球...
...but they had passed the point of no return.
...但他們過了無歸之點.
So they had to go all the way around the moon to get backk...
所以他們不得不完成旅途繞 過月球後返回地球...
...and they were out of contact for hours.
...他們失去聯繫幾個小時.
Everybody waited to see if a bunch of dead guys in a can...
所有人都在等著看是不是一桶死人...
...would pop out the other side.
...會從那邊抛出.
That's me.
那就是我.
On the other side of the moon now...
現在在月球另一邊...
...out of contact...
...失去聯繫...
...and everybody's just going to have to wait till I pop out.
...所有人都得等到我抛出.
The police are here.
警察在這兒.
Did you kknow, Beth...
你知道嗎, Beth...
...in certain South American countries it's still legal...
...在南美一些國家 這麽做還合法...
...to kill your wife if she insults you?
...殺掉侮辱你的老婆?
They're here right now. I'm looking at one right now.
他們就在這兒. 我正看著一個.
Put him on the phone.
給他電話.
-What are we going to do? -Talk to the lKorean guy.
-我們去幹什麽? -跟韓國人談談.
Just start banging on doors.
從門口開始.
What is it?
怎麽了?
Where are you going?
你去哪兒?
I'll be right back.
我很快回來.
I'm sure the guy will let you use his bathroom.
我保證那傢夥會讓你用他的洗手間.
What are you doing?
你在幹什麽?
I know who this guy is!
我知道那傢夥是誰!
Who is he?
是誰?
He had a personalized license plate. What the hell was it?
他有一個私人牌照. 是什麽?
It said, ""D-Fens.""
上面寫"D-Fens."
Defense?
Defense?
D-dash-F-E-N-S.
D-破折號-F-E-N-S.
They said he was on his way home. Go check out his address.
他說在回家路上. 去查查他的地址.
Mr. Lee!
Lee先生!
Defense!
Defense!
Hold it! Back up.
等會! 退後.
You dumb bitch! You cut me off! What's wrong with you!
你他媽的婊子! 你刮著我了! 你怎麽回事!
Move back! Out of the way!
退後! 別擋道!
What are you, a moron?
你是什麽,低能兒?
If I wanted to be in a parking lot, I'd buy a ticket, you dumb bitch!
如果我要進停車場, 我會買票,你他媽個婊子!
Where are you going? You can't go this way.
你去哪兒? 你不能走這兒.
What are you doing?
你們在幹什麽?
Fixing the street! What does it look like?
修路! 看起來像什麽?
Two days ago it was fine.
兩天前還是好的.
You're saying it fell apart in two days?
你是說路在兩天之內壞了?
Well, I guess so.
嗯,我猜是的.
Pardon me, but that's bullshit!
原諒我,但那是胡說!
I don't think anything's wrong with the street.
我覺得路沒任何事.
You're just trying to justify your budgets.
你們只是在迎合預算.
-Are you nuts? -I know how it works!
-你瘋了嗎? -我知道怎麽回事!
If you don't spend your budget, you won't get any money next year.
如果你們不花掉預算, 明年就得不到錢.
I want you to admit nothing's wrong with the street!
我要你們允許路不出毛病!
Fuck you, pal!
操你, 夥計!
You're not going to hold us hostage with these yellow lights and big trucks.
你不能拿我們抵押這些黃燈和大卡車.
I'm just here to keep people from falling in. That's all.
我只是在這兒避免人們掉下去. 就這樣.
I want to hear it from you!
我想聽你說!
What's wrong with the street?
路怎麽回事?
I don't know. I really don't. I think it's a sewer job.
我不知道.真不知道. 我想是下水道工程.
You're lying.
你在撒謊.
What's wrong with the street?
路怎麽了?
Nothing.
沒什麽.
I knew it.
我知道.
I knew it was fine.
我知道它很好.
But I'll give you something to fix.
但我給你們點東西修.
-Oh, Jesus-- -Here!
-哦, 耶穌-- -給!
Hey, Charlie! Oh, please, man!
嗨, Charlie! 哦, 求你, 夥計!
We got a goddamn nut here!
我們有他媽的問題了!
Fucking guy back there with a bazooka!
有個他媽的傢夥拿著火箭筒來了!
Pull that thing off.
拉下來那東西.
-What thing? -That thing.
-什麽東西? -那個東西.
Then pull on both ends. It gets bigger.
然後拉兩端. 會變大.
Like this?
像這樣?
Now flip that thing up. It's your aimer.
現在彈起那個東西. 那是你的瞄準器.
-How do you know about this? -I saw it on TV.
-你怎麽知道的? -電視上看的.
What's the name of the movie?
電影名字是什麽?
What's the name of the movie you're making?
你們拍的電影叫什麽名?
Under Construction. You like it?
正在構思. 你喜歡?
It's all right. Where's the cameras?
不錯. 攝像機呢?
The cameras are-- Just stand back.
攝像機在-- 後退.
What do I do now?
我現在怎麽做?
Just look through the aimer. What are you aiming at?
從瞄準器看. 你瞄什麽?
That yellow monster down there.
那面的黃色怪物.
Look at it and pull the trigger. It's really easy.
看著它扣動扳機. 很容易.
Where's the trigger?
扳機在哪兒?
That one right there.
那邊那個.
But aim first, man.
但先瞄準, 夥計.
Look out!
當心!
-Nothing happened. -Must've been a dud or something.
-沒什麽發生. -一定是個啞彈什麽的.
Cool, man!
真酷, 夥計!
What is it? I'll sic the dog on you!
什麽事? 我放狗咬你!
Police officers, ma'am.
警察, 老媽媽.
How are you?
你好嗎?
Where's the dog?
狗在那裏?
He's dead.
他死了.
-What is it? -We need to ask you some questions.
-什麽事? -我們需要問你幾個問題.
Just a few questions, ma'am.
只是幾個問題, 老媽媽.
What kind of questions?
什麽問題?
Do you have a warrant?
你們有沒有許可?
You invited us in.
你請我們進來的.
Now I'm inviting you out.
現在我請你們出去.
What relation are you to William Foster?
你和 William Foster什麽關係?
What are you saying? He's my son. I don't want you here.
你在說什麽? 他是我兒子. 我不想你在這兒.
Would you look at this! This is really amazing. Amazing!
看看這個! 真是令人吃驚.令人吃驚!
Does he have another house, another place he might call home?
他還有別的地方嗎, 另外他稱爲家的地方?
Now this is a what?
這是什麽?
-A dragon? -Don't touch that!
-一條龍? -別碰!
Why would he do that? This is his home.
他怎麽那麽做? 這是他家.
-I want you to go now. -Did this one melt?
-我想你們馬上離開. -這個融化了嗎?
That one there.
那邊那個.
It's a giraffe, drinking.
那是長頸鹿, 在喝水.
Now, of all of these, which is your very favorite?
那麽,所有這些, 你最喜歡哪個?
Right now, I think this skunk.
此刻, 我想是這個臭鼬.
That's lovely.
那很可愛.
That's not paint.
不是畫的.
You know, his stripe.
你知道, 他的斑紋.
It isn't?
它不是?
It might be, but it's not painted on.
或許是, 但不是畫上的.
It's in the glass.
是在玻璃內.
What the hell?
那是什麽?
It's the groundskeeper.
是草皮護理員.
Well if he is, he's out of uniform. Hey, you there!
如果是, 他沒穿制服. 嗨, 你!
What are you doing there?
你在那邊幹什麽?
Just passing through.
只是經過.
Nobody said you could play through. Get off my hole.
沒人說你可以通過. 離開.
He said he was passing through.
他說他是經過.
He's not a member. Look at the way he's dressed.
他不是會員. 看他穿的.
Would you get off my golf course?!
你能不能離開我的高爾夫球場?!
I am!
我正在!
Go back the way you came!
原路返回!
I don't like his looks. Leave him alone.
我不喜歡他的樣子. 別管他.
What am I paying my dues for? This is my golf course!
我花錢幹什麽? 這是我的高爾夫球場!
If I want to play here, I will!
如果我想玩, 就能玩!
If he gets hit with my Titleist, that's his problem!
如果打到他, 是他的問題!
Don't yell at me. I'm just here playing with you--
別對我吼. 我只是在陪你玩--
Fore!
向前!
Five!
向後!
Wait a minute!
等等!
What the hell you trying to do? IKill me with a golf ball?
你到底要幹什麽? 用高爾夫球殺了我?
It's not enough you got all this land for your little game?
這麽多地方還不夠你玩你的小遊戲嗎?
But you had to kill me with a golf ball?
但你卻要用高爾夫球殺死我?
You should have children playing here, family picnics....
你該讓小孩在這兒玩, 家庭野餐....
You should have a petting zoo...
你該辦個寵物動物園...
...instead of electric carts for you old men with nothing better to do.
...代替你這老頭開著小車無所事事.
Aren't you ashamed of yourself?
你對自己感到羞愧嗎?
-I got to get some help! -What's wrong with you?
-我去找人幫忙! -你怎麽了?
-Help! -Your heart?
-救命! -你的心臟?
Something's wrong with your heart? What can I do?
你的心臟出問題了? 我能做什麽?
Pills! Pills!
藥！藥!
Pills?
藥?
Where are they?
在哪兒?
Cart, cart.
車, 車.
Call the paramedics! My friend just had a heart attack!
叫護士! 我朋友心臟病犯了!
I guess you're out of luck. Your little cart's going to drown.
我想你不走運了. 你的小車要沈了.
Aren't you sorry you didn't let me pass through your golf course?
感到抱歉沒讓我通過嗎?
Now you're going to die wearing that stupid little hat. How does it feel?
現在你要戴著這愚蠢的小帽死了. 感覺怎樣?
This is his room.
這是他的房間.
You're a very neat and tidy lady.
你是個愛整潔的女士.
Oh, he cleans his own room.
奧, 他自己整理房間.
Now don't make me call you a liar.
別讓我說你撒謊.
If he wasn't at work, I'd be afraid to set foot in here.
如果他不工作k, 我不敢踏足此地.
What's he been doing lately?
他最近幹什麽?
Same as ever.
和以往一樣.
Building important things to protect us from the Communists.
造重要的東西避免我們受共産主義攻擊.
He works at Notec.
他在 Notec工作.
The defense plant.
那個軍工廠.
D-Fens.
D-Fens.
Why don't you call and see if you can get him on the horn?
你爲什麽到處去看看?
So what's going on with your son?
那麽你兒子怎麽樣?
-How do you mean? -You know exactly what I mean.
-你什麽意思? -你知道我的意思.
Sometimes he sits through an entire meal without saying a word.
又是他一整頓飯一言不發.
He just shovels food into his mouth like a machine.
只像機器一樣鏟飯入嘴.
I get so nervous...
我很緊張...
...I can't swallow.
...無法下咽.
I'll sit there with the same piece of food in my mouth.
我坐著幹嚼同一片食物.
I have to spit it on the plate. When I do, he looks at me...
我不得不吐在盤子裏. 我這麽做時, 他看著我...
...Iike he'd like to kill me.
...就像要殺了我.
Don't tell him I said that.
別告訴他我說的.
I promise I won't.
我保證不會.
I try not to be a burden. I'm not just talking financial.
我儘量不成爲負擔. 我不提經濟.
How could you be a burden to anyone?
你怎麽會是什麽人的負擔?
If William, or Bill, as I like to call him--
如果 William或Bill, 如果我要叫他--
He likes Bill. I call him Bill too.
他喜歡 Bill. 我也叫他Bill.
If Bill said he was going home...
如果 Bill 說他回家...
...could he have meant where his wife and child live?
...會不會是他老婆孩子住的地方?
Ex-wife. We shouldn't be in here.
前妻. 我們不該在這兒.
Ex-wife, right. Elizabeth. What's her maiden name?
前妻, 對. Elizabeth. 她娘家姓是什麽?
Trevino. She was part ltalian. You know how they are.
Trevino. 她有義大利血統. 你這到他們什麽樣.
-Where's Elizabeth now? -I wouldn't know.
-Elizabeth 現在在哪兒? -我不會知道.
You don't know where your grandchild lives?
你不知道你孫女住哪兒?
He doesn't want me to know. He blames me for what happened.
他不想讓我知道. 他因發生的事埋怨我.
What's the word?
有什麽?
He was fired over a month ago.
他一月前被解雇了.
Where has he been going every day?
他每天都去哪兒?
Where has he been eating his lunch?
去哪兒吃午飯?
Why are you putting barbed wire in that fence?
爲什麽在圍欄上架鐵絲網?
Is this how you rich people have fun?
你們富人以此取樂?
You put barbed wire on the fence, so innocent people...
你們在圍欄上架鐵絲網, 就能讓無辜的人...
...can cut their hands?
...劃傷手?
No, please, I'm the caretaker.
不, 請, 我是臨時看管.
It's just a barbecue.
只是個烤肉野餐.
Dr. Ashcroft has let us do this before.
Ashcroft醫生讓我在這兒.
You don't live here?
你不住這兒?
Is it really necessary to tell them?
真的需要告訴他們?
Tell who?
告訴誰?
Altmore Security.
安全管理員.
Aren't you with them?
你不和他們一起?
No, please!
不,求你!
It's okay, honey. It's okay, baby.
沒事,親愛的. 沒事, 寶貝.
What kind of doctor lives here?
住這兒的是什麽醫生?
Plastic surgeon.
整形外科.
Plastic surgery bought all this?
整形外科買的所有這些?
Guess I'm in the wrong racket.
我猜我走錯路了.
They have correspondence courses in plastic surgery?
他們有整形外科的函授課嗎?
I lost my job.
我失業了.
Actually, I didn't lose it. It lost me.
實際上,我沒失去它. 它失去了我.
I'm overeducated, underskilled.
我有知識有技能.
Maybe it's the other way around. I forget.
或許還有條路. 我忘了.
But I'm obsolete.
但是我廢了.
I'm not economically viable.
我沒有信貸能力了.
I can't even support my own kid.
我甚至不能養活孩子.
Are you hurt?
你受傷了?
I'm sorry. I didn't hurt you, sweetheart. I'm sorry.
我很抱歉. 我沒傷你, 甜心. 我很抱歉.
It's all right.
沒事.
It's your hand.
是你的手.
You cut your hand.
你劃傷了手.
It's my hand.
是我的手.
Please take me with you.
請讓我陪著你.
They won't do anything if I'm with you.
我和你一起他們什麽也不會做.
Just let them go.
只是讓她們走.
What do you think? You think I want to hurt your family?
你在想什麽? 你覺得我要傷害你的家人?
I have a family of my own.
我有自己的家庭.
You don't believe me?
你不相信我?
We believe you.
我們相信你.
That's where I'm going. I'm going home to see my family.
我正要去. 我正回家去看我的家人.
It's my little girl's birthday today.
今天是我小女兒的生日.
We were going to have a barbecue, like you guys, and...
我們要辦烤肉野餐, 就像你們,還要...
...she was going to play outside...
...帶她出去玩...
...and my wife would hold my hand...
...我老婆抓著我的手...
...and talk about grown-up things.
...說些積極的事.
And then when it got dark...
等天黑了...
...we'd all go to sleep together.
...我們一起睡.
We'd sleep together in the dark.
我們一起睡在黑暗裏.
And everything...
所有事...
...would be just like it was before.
...都和以前一樣.
You can't leave. Believe me, something's happened to him.
你不能走. 相信我, 他出了些事.
It doesn't take all day to drive from Pasadena to Venice.
從 Pasadena 到Venice用不了一整天.
That doesn't constitute a threatening phone call.
這構不成電話威脅.
The guy was talking about Star Trekk or something.
那傢夥在說著玩.
-Just getting a kick out of scaring-- -Please don't leave.
-把恐懼放掉-- -請別離開.
There's only one thing you can do to really feel safer.
只有一件事能讓你感到安全些.
Next time there's a proposition...
下次給你個建議...
...to cut the number of patrol cars on the street, vote no, okay?
...記下大街上的巡邏車號碼, 打零分, 好嗎?
Have a nice day.
一天愉快.
What have you found so far?
找到什麽了嗎?
No luck on Foster-T revino.
Foster-T revino沒什麽幸運.
Go straight to the maiden name.
直接找娘家姓.
I've got something on an Army-Navy store.
我在軍品商店找到些東西.
Where?
哪兒?
Here.
這兒.
Jesus, Prendergast, I was there!
耶穌, Prendergast, 我去過那兒!
That guy was a prick.
那傢夥是個刺頭.
You know what else he was?
你知道他還是什麽嗎?
Murdered. They found him stuffed in his own display case.
被殺了.他的屍體在自己的儲藏室發現的.
Oh, my God!
哦,我的上帝!
Here, I'll help you change the--
給, 我幫你換--
You know what they did?
你知道他們做什麽了?
They turned our ice-cream parlor...
他們把冷飲店轉給...
...into a Southwest-American, New Age thing.
...了一個南美人, 新世紀式的.
I went to buy a rocking horse.
我在那兒買的搖擺木馬.
All I could find was a unicorn with an Indian on top of it.
只能找到騎獨角獸的印第安人.
Can you believe that, Elizabeth? Can you believe it?
你能相信嗎, Elizabeth? 你能相信嗎?
Come on!
來!
Where are we going? When's my birthday?
我們去哪兒? 什麽時候過生日?
Some Gl Joe gave a geezer a heart attack at the golf course...
高爾夫球場有個 Gl Joe 把個怪老頭搞心臟病了...
...and accosted a family right next door.
...接著到隔壁聊天去了.
A Gl Joe?
一個Gl Joe?
He's wearing the kind of jacket you find in an Army-Navy store.
他穿著你在軍品商店發現的那種夾克.
I found her! Trevino, Elizabeth.
我找到了! Trevino, Elizabeth.
Don't tell me.
別告訴我.
Venice.
Venice.
How'd you know?
你怎麽知道的?
Where else would an ltalian move to?
一個義大利人還會去哪兒?
Lookk what I got.
看我拿來什麽.
We got a puppy.
我們有個小狗.
Happy birthday to you
祝你生日快樂
Hi, puppy!
嗨, 小狗!
No answer at the ex-wife.
前妻沒回音.
-You send the cavalry? -No, Pacific Division are pricks.
-你派了巡邏隊? -不, 治安隊是刺頭.
They can't send units to the same address three times in a day...
他們不能一天派三次人去同一地方...
...to comfort some hysterical woman.
...去安撫一個歇斯底里的女人.
-What do you want to do? -Go to Venice.
-你要去幹什麽? -去 Venice.
Get that.
接一下.
Prendergast here.
這兒是Prendergast.
Who the fuck is this?
這他媽是誰?
Shit. It's your wife.
媽的. 是你老婆.
Oh, boy. Hon?
哦, 親愛的?
Yeah, "hon." I know who that was!
是, "親愛的"我知道那是什麽!
Mr. Peepers just scratched the shit out of me...
Peepers 先生剛給我通了便...
...and I'm bleeding like a stuck pig.
...我血流不止.
Something important's come up.
有些大事發生了.
What am l? Dog vomit?
我是誰? 狗屎?
Your wife says she's bleeding to death...
你老婆說他要流血致死了...
...and you say something important has come up?
...你卻說有大事發生了?
-When are you coming home? -I don't know.
-你什麽時候回家? -我不知道.
Don't tell me you don't know.
別跟我說你不知道.
I want to know when the hell you're coming home, now!
我要知道你到底什麽時候回家, 馬上!
Amanda, shut up!
Amanda, 閉嘴!
Did you hear me? Shut up!
你聽到了嗎? 閉嘴!
I'll get home when I'm finished, not a second before. Is that clear?
我做完以後回家, 一秒也不提前. 清楚嗎?
Is that clear?
清楚嗎?
You don't have to bite my head off!
你不必大喊大叫!
And you have dinner ready and waiting for me, okay?
你做好飯等我, 好嗎?
And leave the skin on the chicken! All right?
給雞去皮! 好嗎?
Goodbye.
再見.
Shit!
媽的!
Let's go!
走吧!
Surprise!
驚喜!
I' m sorry, Prendergast!
我很抱歉, Prendergast!
We tried and tried, but could not fit your fucking name on the cake!
我們試了又試, 還是不能把你他媽的名字放上去!
Congratulations. You made it out alive!
祝賀你. 你活著出來了!
Listen, listen.
聽著,聽著.
All right, hold it, hold it.
好了, 等等, 等等.
Ladies and gentlemen, the moment you've been waiting for:
女士們先生們, 你們期盼的時刻:
This afternoon's entertainment, Miss Suzie!
下午的娛樂專案, Suzie小姐!
Suzie Q!
Suzie Q!
Do your thing!
開始你的!
Is this the retiring boy?
這個是那退休的男孩?
Wait, wait! This is great, guys.
等等,等等! 著很好,夥計們.
This is great. I appreciate it, but I can't stay.
這很好. 我很感激,但我不能待著.
Jesus! What's your problem? You afraid of women too?
耶穌! 你怎麽回事? 你還害怕女人?
I don't blame him. You ever met his wife?
我不責怪他. 你們沒見過他老婆?
What did you say?
你說什麽?
-What? -What did you say?
-什麽? -你說什麽?
Nothing.
沒什麽.
We don't have time for this.
我們沒時間浪費.
You're right.
你是對的.
Ready, honey?
準備好了, 親愛的?
Happy Birthday to you
祝你生日快樂
Happy Birthday...
生日快樂...
...to you
...祝你
No cakke for you?
你沒蛋糕?
If she doesn't want it, don't force her.
如果她不想要, 別強迫她.
Okkay, you can have the teddy.
好的, 你可以要連體褲.
Time to go horsy!
到時間騎馬了!
It's okkay. Horsy! It's okkay.
好的. 騎馬! 好的.
Giddyap, giddyap.
駕,駕.
-She doesn't want to. -Just put her on the horse!
-她不想要. -把她放馬上就好!
There we go! Horsy ride. Giddyap!
走羅! 騎馬. 駕!
She doesn't want to.
她不想要.
Put her on the horse!
把她放馬上!
You can't force her.
你不能強迫她.
I bought her the goddamn horse.
我給她買得他媽的旋轉木馬.
Here we go! Horsy ride.
走吧! 騎馬.
You're scaring her! I want you to stop this!
你嚇著她了! 我想要你停下!
Come on, honey. It's her birthday. It's the pier.
來吧,親愛的. 這是她的生日. 這是碼頭.
It's your favorite place. You love the pier.
這是你最喜歡的地方. 你愛這碼頭.
Why do you do this?
你爲什麽這麽做?
Take the back.
到後邊去.
Freeze!
別動!
You okay?
你還好?
-l' m all right. -Somebody get an ambulance.
-我還好. -去叫輛救護車.
Get an ambulance! Call 9 1 1! Get an ambulance!
叫輛救護車! 打 9 1 1! 叫輛救護車!
T ell them an officer's been shot! Go, go, go! Get an ambulance!
告訴他們一個警察受傷了! 去, 去, 去! 叫輛救護車!
Be careful!
小心!
Go get the bastard!
去抓那個婊子養的!
He's still dressed like Gl Joe!
他還穿著 Gl Joe!
Daddy! Mommy, look! Daddy!
爸爸! 媽媽, 看! 爸爸!
Hi, honey.
嗨, 親愛的.
I thought I'd find you here.
我知道會在這兒找到你.
Leave us alone!
離開我們!
What? I can't talk to my wife?
什麽?我不能跟老婆說話?
I'm not your wife anymore.
我不再是你老婆了.
No? Sugar, does this ring a bell? "Till death do us part"?
不? 甜心, 這不令人回憶? "至死不分"?
Do you remember that?
還記得嗎?
I'm sorry.
我很抱歉.
Sorry, sorry.
抱歉, 抱歉.
What're you doing?
你在幹什麽?
I'm coming home from a hard day at the office.
我從繁重的工作中回家.
God bless the working stiffs!
上帝保佑那機械勞動!
Please, leave her alone!
求你,離開她!
You're so big!
你這麽大了!
How'd you get so big?
你怎麽長這麽大的?
I missed it.
我錯失了.
They stole it from me, honey.
他們偷走了它, 親愛的.
Don't worry. They're not going to take it anymore.
別擔心. 他們再拿不走了.
Bill, listen, please.
Bill, 聽著,求你.
You've got to stop this!
你得停下!
You need help.
你需要幫助.
You're sick.
你病了.
Sick?
病?
You want to see sick?
你想看病人?
Take a walk around this town. That's sick.
繞城散步. 那才是病.
You ain't kidding.
你不是小孩.
Would you believe that I used to fish right here?
你相信我慣常在這兒釣魚?
This very spot?
這個地方?
Now they tell you, "Don't eat the fish. It's poisonous."
現在他們告訴你, "別吃魚. 污染了."
You can't even swim in the water.
你甚至不能下水游泳.
It'll give you some kind of bacterial infection.
會讓你細菌感染.
How's that for sick?
對病怎麽樣?
I'm having a private moment with my family. Leave us alone.
我正在和家人私人聊天. 離遠點.
I'm leaving soon.
我很快離開.
I'm retiring to Arizona. Lake Havasu City.
我要退休去Arizona. Havasu湖市.
Ever been there?
沒去過那兒?
That's not what I mean!
那不是我的意思!
They call it a lake, but it's really just a big bowl of muddy water.
他們叫它湖, 但它實際上是一碗渾水.
But the wife thinks it's paradise.
但我老婆覺得那是天堂.
Everybody has their own idea of what paradise is.
每個人都有他自己的天堂標準.
Take me, for instance.
看看我, 做個例子.
You know what I thought paradise was?
你知道我的天堂是什麽?
-What? -lf you'll excuse me.
-什麽? -如果你們允許我.
Making babies.
養孩子.
Ain't that a kick?
那不是病嗎?
This your little girl?
這是你的小女兒?
Beautiful.
漂亮.
She's special.
她很特別.
You know, my wife never was cut out for motherhood.
你知道, 我老婆沒有切斷爲母之道.
She did it all for me.
她爲我做了.
Went through all that pain, lost her figure.
忍受所有的痛苦, 失去身材.
Then the kid went to sleep one night, never woke up.
然後那孩子一晚睡去, 再也沒醒.
They called it ""lnfant Death...
他們叫這個 "小兒...
...Syndrome."
...麻痹至死."
But she wasn't an infant. She was 2 years old.
但她不是小兒了. 她兩歲大了.
She was a big girl.
她是個大女孩了.
She was our baby.
她不是嬰兒.
Here, darling, this is for you. Here you go.
給, 親愛的,這個給你. 拿著.
What can you do?
你能做什麽?
If she'd been hit by a drunk driver....
如果她被一個醉酒司機撞到....
But who do you blame when they just don't wake up?
但是她只是一睡不醒我去責備誰?
Thank you, sweetheart.
謝謝, 甜心.
There's a guy back there with a gun!
有個人拿著槍來了!
No! Don't!
不! 不要!
Elizabeth, no!
Elizabeth, 不!
Freeze! You're under arrest.
別動! 你被捕了.
Get out of here! Go on!
出去! 快!
Freeze!
別動!
-What were you going to do? -I don't know!
-你要幹什麽? -我不知道!
Guys like you always say that!
你這樣的人總這麽說!
You know exactly what you were going to do, kill your wife and child!
你知道你要幹什麽, 殺了你老婆孩子!
Then it'd be too late to turn back. It'd be easy to kill yourself.
然後覆水難收. 殺了自己很容易.
Let's go meet some nice policemen. They're good guys. Let's go.
走去見見警察們. 他們是好人. 走吧.
I'm the bad guy?
我是壞人嗎?
How did that happen?
這是怎麽發生的?
I did everything they told me to.
我做了他們讓我做的所有事.
Did you know I build missiles?
你知不知道我製造導彈?
I help to protect America.
我保衛美國.
You should be rewarded for that.
應該爲此受獎勵.
Instead, they give it to the plastic surgeon. They lied to me.
然而, 他們卻給了整形外科. 他們對我撒謊.
Is that what this is about? You' re angry because you got lied to?
這又怎麽了? 你因被騙而發怒?
Is that why my dinner's drying out in the oven?
這是爲什麽我的午餐爆出烤箱嗎?
They lie to everybody. They lie to the fish!
他們對所有人撒謊. 他們對魚撒謊!
That doesn't give you any right to do what you did today.
這沒給你任何權力去幹你今天所幹的.
The only thing that makes you special is that little girl. Now let's go.
讓你特別的只有那個小女孩. 現在走吧.
Let's go!
走吧!
Sure was hot today, wasn't it?
今天很熱, 不是嗎?
He has a gun! There, on the pier!
他有槍! 那兒, 碼頭上!
IKeep this crowd back! Let's get some backup!
我疏散人群! 去叫些後援!
You know, I got a gun.
你知道, 我有支槍.
In my pocket.
在我口袋.
I got lots of guns.
我有很多槍.
Stay there. Don't move!
站哪兒. 別動!
You want to draw?
你想拖延?
Let's not. Let's call it a day.
別. 我們收工吧.
Now come on.
現在來吧.
It's perfect.
這很美.
Showdown...
攤牌...
...between the sheriff and the bad guy?
...州長和壞人之間?
It's beautiful.
這很漂亮.
On three.
數三下.
This doesn't have to be the end, Bill. You have a choice.
沒必要玩完, Bill. 你還有選擇.
See, my little girl is dead. I don't have a choice. You do!
看, 我小女兒死了. 我沒選擇了. 你有!
No, you have two choices:
不, 你有兩個選項:
I can kill you.
我可以殺了你.
Or you can kill me...
或者你可以殺了我...
...and my little girl can get the insurance.
...然後我的小女兒能得到保險.
One....
一....
You want to see her grow up?
你想看她長大?
Behind bars?
在監獄裏?
Two....
二....
Don't do this. Please.
別這麽做. 請.
-Let's go! -Three.
-來吧! -三.
I would have got you.
我想像你一樣.
What cooperation was there between the Pacific Division and Downtown?
治安隊和警局有什麽協作關係?
Not to denigrate the Venice Police Department...
不是說Venice派出所的壞話...
...but it was one of our fellows that put this together.
...但是是我們的人搞定的.
Prendergast!
Prendergast!
This is Sergeant Prendergast. Damn fine work, Prendergast.
這是Prendergast警官. 他媽的幹得好, Prendergast.
Fuck you, Captain Yardley. Fuck you very much!
他媽的,Yardley隊長. 你真他媽的!
I can't believe-- Did he just say that?
我不能相信-- 他只說那個?
You're welcome.
沒什麽.
-You still here? -Afraid so.
-你還在這? -恐怕是的.
We've stabilized her. She'll be all right.
我們穩定她了. 她會沒事.
I'll see you at the hospital.
我會去醫院看你.
How are you doing?
你怎麽樣?
I haven't told her yet.
我還沒告訴她.
Oh, shit!
哦, 他媽的!
It's her birthday. What should I do?
今天是她生日. 我該做什麽?
Tell her tomorrow.
明天告訴她.
Let her have her little party.
讓她有個小派對.
-What's your name, darling? -Adele.
-你叫什麽, 親愛的? -Adele.
Adele?
Adele?
That's a nice name.
真好聽.
If I had a little girl, I'd want her to be named Adele.
如果我有個女兒, 我要叫她Adele.
-What's yours? -Mine?
-你的呢? -我的?
My name is mud.
我叫泥漿.
Your name is not mud.
你的名字不是泥漿.
It will be when my wife finds out that...
當我老婆發現我還是警察...
...I'm still a cop.
...就會是了.
Excuse me.
打攪.
Sergeant just signed us out.
警官讓我們出去.
-All right, let's eat. -Where you want to go?
-好的, 去吃飯. -你想去哪兒?
Let's go around the corner and get one of those things....
四處轉轉找一家....
Lookk what I got!
看看我得到什麽!
Just call him, "Hi, Puppy. "
叫他, "嗨,小狗. "
Hi, Puppy.
嗨, 小狗.
There we go. We got everybody there.
走吧. 大家都在看.
We got everybody--
大家都在--
" Falling Down" The End
" 怒火風暴" -=結束=-